(Leonard:)That's not what she's doing, Leslie.
She's trying to shore up her self-esteem.
It has nothing to do with sex.
(Leslie:)Everything has to do with sex.
(Howard:)Mm. Testify.
(Leslie:)I'm not touching that.
- Leslie, you are way off base here.
- Now, hang on, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)While I have no respect for Leslie as a
scientist or a human being for that matter...
(Sheldon:)...we have to concede
her undeniable expertise...
(Sheldon:)...in the interrelated fields of promiscuity
and general sluttiness.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Leslie:)My point is that Tinkerbell
just needs to get her some.
(Sheldon:)Some what?
Oh, yes, some sexual intercourse.
(Howard:)I'll take the bullet.
- Excuse me, this whole idea's insane.
- Enough debate. I'm going to take action.
(Gablehauser(as phone rings):)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Are you currently involved
in a sexual relationship?
(Sheldon:)- No.
- Would you like to be?